--==本字幕由 字幕庫 獨家首發==--
更多影視字幕 請訪問 http://www.zimuku.net/
原創OCR：賈寶玉  字幕調教：字幕庫-小小草
我天
Fuck me.
真不敢相信我會死在這種地方
I can't believe I'm going to die in this place.
但在這麼遙遠的地方 我就能幹更多壞事
But, as far as headstones go, a man could do a lot worse.
我叫查理沃爾夫
I'm Charlie Wolfe.
當你躺在這裏 等待死亡的降臨
And as I lie here, waiting for death's cold embrace,
我不禁問自己
I find myself asking the question,
事情怎麼會變成這樣
"How the fuck did it come to this?"
我才不會死 我要活得更好
I don't die. I thrive.
該死
Fuck.
Fuck!
喂 是我
Yeah? Yeah.
不好意思 你先等會
I'm... I'm sorry. Could you hang on one second?
好的 我一小時以後到
Yeah, I'll be there in an hour.
早上好 微博牙科醫院
Good morning. Doctor Webb Dental Surgery.
露西 我是愛麗絲
Hi, Lucy. This is Alice.
你好 愛麗絲
Hi, Alice.
南森下午有空嗎
Do you think Nathan can see me this afternoon?
我身體疼痛的不行
I'm actually in a lot of pain.
可以 我幫你安排一下時間
Sure. I think we can fit you in.
兩點怎麼樣
How's 2:00?
好的 兩點見
Perfect. I'll see you at 2:00.
好的 一會見
Alright. See you later.
南森
Nathan!
拜託 老兄
Come on, mate.
再幫我最後一次
Please just sort me out this one last time.
五萬塊押西爾弗贏
Fifty thousand on Silver Tsar to win.
謝謝 你最好了
Thanks. You're a saint.
南森
Nathan!
計劃有變 她今天要來
Change of plans. She's coming today.
我還沒準備好
I'm not ready.
那沒辦法
We've got no choice.
把我的牙科病歷換上 把我的車開到沙地去
Switch my dental records and let's get my car to the quarry.
媽的
Shit.
她到了
She's here.
牙科病歷換好了嗎
Have you swapped those dental records?
-嗨    -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
-抱歉我遲到了  -沒關係
- I'm sorry I'm late. - It's okay.
-怎麼回事  -我撞到門了
- What happened? - Oh, I hit the door.
真可憐
Oh, you poor thing!
南森 愛麗絲來了
Nathan, Alice is here!
-嗨 南森
-嗨 愛麗絲
- Hi, Nathan. - Hi, Alice.
好的
Okay.
-好 進來吧  -好
- Yeah, shall we? - Yeah.
我需要打針嗎
Do I really need an injection?
需要 我會輕一點的
Yes. But I will be gentle.
我應該不用…
I think I...
躺好 張嘴
Now, lie back... and open.
可真磨磨蹭蹭 解決了嗎
Took you long enough. Is she out?
沒動靜了
Cold.
-拿走戒指  -好
- Grab her jewelry. - Yeah.
-看見什麼了  -沒看見
- Did you see something? - No.
汽油準備好了嗎
You remember the petrol?
什麼都要我操心嗎
Must I think of everything?
路上有加油站
There's a garage on the way.
快點 我等你
Don't take forever. I'll be waiting.
接下來是第五個報道 黑人聚居區…
Ready to go in the fifth event, Blacktown...
西爾弗出現了…
Silver Tsar's coming up...
西爾弗被帶到比賽場地
Here's Silver Tsar taking to the outside
歷經磨練的幸運兒點亮了賽場
and the well-tried favorite lights up.
西爾弗的對手是黑人區的小伙子Lad和Daytone
It's Silver Tsar racing the Blacktown Lad and Daytone.
-他佔據了領先地位  -快上
- He's taken over the running. - Get up!
這位幸運兒當前形勢十分樂觀
And the favorite's looking really good at the moment.
他甩開了對手
He raced two lengths in front of...
別這樣 別這樣 拜託 別這樣
Not now, not now. Please, not now.
西爾弗暫時佔據領先地位 但他看起來很疲憊
Silver Tsar has the lead but he's getting tired.
Daytone出現在身後 麥迪遜羅斯也追上來了
Daytone's coming back and so is Madison Rose.
噢 出現轉機了 幸運兒被超過了
Oh, there's a fall! The favorite's down!
-該死  -西爾弗落在了後面
- Shit! - Silver Tsar's fallen.
-真不敢相信  -媽的
- You wouldn't believe it. - Shit!
-媽的 媽的 -勝利就在眼前 他卻沒有把握住...
- Shit, shit, shit! - Victory in his sights and he's down...
只剩最後50米 他沒有創造奇跡
...wonder of the world, and down he went with only 50m to go.
世事難料 這就是比賽
Que sera. That's racing, I guess.
可惜的是丟了錢的投注者
It's bad luck for the punters that they lose their money.
媽的
Fucking hell!
該死
Fuck!
南森 最近怎麼樣
Nathan, how are you going?
很好 就是輪胎壞了
I'm alright. I've just... just got a flat.
哦 是嗎 需要幫忙嗎
Oh, yeah. Need a hand?
不用 沒事 我拿出來了
Nah, all good. I got it.
包在我身上了
No worries at all, mate.
謝謝了
Thanks.
你還在計劃離開嗎
You still planning on leaving?
我可不只是計劃
I'm way beyond planning.
我正在行動 今天就走
I'm doing. Today.
挺好的
Good on you.
還需要別的嗎
Do you need anything else?
嗯 你有大瓶的水嗎
Yeah... you got any large waters?
-有 我去後面拿 -謝謝
- Yeah, I've got some out the back. - Thanks.
你來旅遊的嗎
Are you a tourist?
差不多吧
Something like that.
給你
Here you go.
不是冰的水行嗎
Sorry it's not cold. Just the one?
行的 再加20塊的油
Yeah, better give me $20 worth of petrol.
好的
Yeah, no worries.
這裏禁止抽煙
You can't smoke in here.
謝謝 迪倫 祝你好運
Cheers, Dylan. Good luck.
你怎麼這麼慢
What kept you this time?
我有個手術
I got a flat.
你事情怎麼這麼多
It's always something with you.
出了點意外
It was an accident.
那就抓緊時間
Come on, then. Let's get on with it.
你才需要上保險
It's you we should be insuring, not me.
-噢 媽的 -臥槽
- Oh... shit! - Oh, fuck!
南森
Nathan!
別擔心 會沉下去的
Don't worry. It'll sink.
等一會
Soon.
下去幫忙啊
Get in there!
好的
Alright.
臥槽 太冷了
Fuck, Luce, it's really cold.
走吧
Let's go.
臥槽
Fuck me.
把包拿好
Grab the bag.
-汽油呢  -在後座
- Petrol? - In the back seat.
這什麼雞巴玩意兒
What the fuck is this?
汽油啊
It's the petrol.
就這一點嗎
Where's the rest of it?
這些夠了
That'll be enough.
啊
Argh!
愛麗絲
Alice...
冷靜
calm down.
臥槽
Fuck!
南森 快起來 她跑了
Nathan, get up! She's getting away!
哦 臥槽了
Oh, fuck's sake!
喂
Oi!
露西
Lucy!
媽的
Fuck.
-嗨   -動手吧
- Hey. - Let's fucking do this.
-她在哪  -後座
- Where is she? - In the back seat.
-戒指在前面 -是的
- Jewelry's on the dash. - Yeah.
快塞進去
Just get her in.
太難塞了
Not so fucking easy.
別這麼溫柔 直接塞進去
Hey, you don't have to be so gentle. Just get her in there.
好的
Okay.
對不起了 愛麗絲
Sorry, Alice.
再見 愛麗絲
Goodbye, Alice.
我不用了 不行 我在工作
No, I'm fine. I can't. I'm working.
好極了
Great.
準備好
Alright, ready?
乾杯
Cheers!
我答應來幫忙 不是說你可以悠閒地在這坐著的
I agreed to help out but not so you can sit around on your fucking ass.
我一會就好
I'll be another minute.
-傑克 我們談談  -現在不行
- Jack, we need to talk. - Not now.
你的婚姻是一場玩笑
Your marriage is a joke.
她已經完全放棄你了
She's given up on your whole pathetic act.
你知道你是…
Do you know that you're the la...
夠了
Enough.
你怎麼不跟你游手好閒的老公
Why don't you and your deadbeat husband
好好管理你們的生意
mind your own fucking business?
傑克 你是我哥
Jack, you're my brother.
我不能袖手旁觀
I can't just stand by and watch this happen.
說完了了嗎
Are you done?
你打電話了嗎
Have you made that call?
雇用他 跟蹤她
Hire him and have her followed.
如果不是 我就什麼都不管了
If I'm wrong, then I won't say another word.
傑克 我們需要進一點特基拉酒
Jack, we need to get more tequi...
你什麼時候有槍的
When did you get a gun?
發生了什麼事
Is everything okay?
坐下
Sit down.
端起來
Pick it up.
把槍放下
Please put the gun down.
我叫你端起來
I said pick it fucking up.
你知道我有多愛你嗎
Do you have any idea how much I love you?
你不愛我
You don't love me.
你只想控制我
You just want to control me.
愛麗絲
Alice.
你在跟別人約會嗎
Are you seeing someone else?
這種事我沒辦法解決
'Cause I couldn't handle something like that.
我只能看你死
I'd sooner see you dead.
我要走了
I need to go.
喂?
Yeah.
不好意思 你等會
Sorry, just hold on a sec.
好的 我一小時後到那
Yeah, I'll be there in an hour.
-你在幹嘛  -傑克 你弄疼我了
- What are you doing? - Jack, you're hurting me.
你偷偷摸摸地幹嘛
What are you fucking doing sneaking around?
我沒有偷偷摸摸
I wasn't sneaking around.
這是你最後一次打我了
That's the last time you hit me.
愛麗絲 我錯了
Alice, I'm sorry!
你牙齒碎了
Yeah, your tooth is chipped.
我只有這些
Sorry, it's all I've got.
謝謝
Thank you.
你一個人可以嗎
You'll be okay on your own for a few?
怎麼了 你要去哪
Why? Where are you going?
我要去拜訪一下傑克
I'm gonna pay Jack a visit.
迪倫... 迪倫
Dylan... Dylan.
迪倫
Dylan!
過來
Come here.
別走
Stay with me.
有些人要受點教訓
Somebody needs to sort that prick out.
別走
Stay with me.
求你
Please?
拜託
Please.
傑克不會經常這樣
Jack wasn't always like this.
別給他找借口
Doesn't excuse what he does.
你知道他之前跟我說什麼嗎
You know what he told me earlier?
如果我跟別的男人在一起他就要我死
That he'd sooner see me dead than with another guy.
他真的這麼說了嗎
He actually said that?
最恐怖的是...
The scariest part...
說話的時候他拿槍指著我
...is that he was pointing this at me when he said that.
操他媽的
Fucking hell.
還好我們明天要離開了
Good thing we're leaving tomorrow.
你確定你要走嗎
You sure you want to go?
當然了
Of course I'm sure.
但是你還沒有賣掉你的加油站
But you haven't sold the garage yet.
看來時間很緊迫
Things will be tight.
錢是個大問題
Money's always a problem when you don't have much.
我會找工作掙錢
I'll get a job.
我們可以掙很多錢
We can make enough for the both of us.
我可以幫你安排一下時間
Sure. I think we can fit you in.
兩點怎麼樣？
How's 2:00?
好的 兩點見
Perfect. I'll see you at 2:00.
好的 等會見
Alright. See you later.
南森
Nathan!
你酒醒了嗎
Are you sober?
差不多
Mostly.
對不起 愛麗絲
I'm sorry, Alice.
你總是說對不起
You're always sorry.
-喂  -我是查理沃爾夫
- Yeah. - This is Charlie Wolfe.
稍等
Hang on.
喂 把門關上
Oi. Shut the door?
說
Yeah.
有些東西你可以看看
I have something you might want to see.
好
Okay.
我過去嗎
Should I drop in?
不用
No.
知道岩石那邊的停車場嗎
You know the car park by Merchant Rock?
我一小時後到
I'll be there in an hour.
嗨 布魯斯
Hey, Bruce.
傑克在哪
Where's Jack?
在他辦公室
In his office.
你一定累了吧
You must be tired.
是 有點
Yeah, a little.
在小鎮兩頭跑
Running around town the way you do.
日夜兼程的
All hours of the day and night.
什麼
Excuse me?
-布魯斯  -傑克
- Bruce. - Jack. The very man.
我正在品嚐你的威士忌
Just checking on that case of whisky you promised.
過一會找你行嗎 我正要出門
Is later alright, mate? I'm just heading out.
好啊 別太久就行
Yeah. Long as it's not too much later.
對吧
Right?
給我你的車鑰匙
Give us your car keys.
你車子怎麼了
What's wrong with your car?
還在修理廠
It's still at the paint shop.
會很久嗎
Will you be long?
不確定
As long as it takes.
我兩點鐘要去見牙醫
I have an appointment with Nathan at 2:00.
該死
Fuck.
媽的
Shit.
沃爾夫
Wolfe!
沒想到這麼快就能接到你的電話
I didn't expect your call so soon.
是對手太鬆懈
Sometimes they make it too easy.
這是昨晚的
This was last night?
我天
Jesus.
給我帶什麼了嗎
Do you have something for me?
這個給我
I'm keeping this.
拿去吧
Be my guest.
就是為你準備的
I bought it just for you.
你打算呆幾天
You feel like staying on for a few days?
在這呆著沒意思
No sense hanging around.
有你感興趣的東西
I've got something for you, if you're interested.
你說
I'm listening.
五萬美金怎麼樣
How does 50 grand sound?
是筆大買賣
Like a dirty job.
你繼續說
And I'm still listening.
殺了我妻子
I want you to kill my wife.
讓這賤人消失
Make the bitch disappear.
傑克 你會把事情變得很麻煩
Jack, you've worked yourself into a knot over this thing.
沒關係
Fine.
你現在還不夠冷靜
You're reacting badly to some bad news.
-慢慢考慮  -我想清楚了
- Just take some time. - My mind is clear.
這可是一條不歸路 明白嗎
What you're talking about is a one-way street. You understand?
可沒有回頭的機會了
Once you start, there is no going back.
我已經警告過她了
She's had fair warning.
她明知故犯
She knew the consequences and she did it anyway.
所以殺了她
So fuck her.
你不想要錢嗎
You want my money or not?
你有現金嗎
Do you have that sort of cash just lying around?
有很多
It's covered.
我是說私房錢 這工作可沒有什麼收據
I mean untraceable. This kind of job doesn't come with a receipt.
都已經準備好了
I told you, it's covered.
這是信任的問題
There is, of course, the issue of trust.
我相信你
I trust you.
我知道 但是我怎麼確定
Yes, but how can I be sure
你不會耍我呢
you're not gonna go soft on me, Jack?
我們要相信彼此
Well, we'll have to trust each other.
你和你妻子信任彼此嗎
Did you and your wife ever trust each other?
你不想接著單 好吧 忘了我說過什麼
You don't want the job? Fine. Forget I asked.
我可沒不答應
I don't remember saying no.
那你就是答應了
So are you saying yes?
好吧 我干
Alright, I'll do it.
但是5萬不夠
But not for 50 grand.
你要多少
How much?
我要的價格比這高一倍
My rate's an even one.
6萬嗎
Sixty?
不 10萬
No, 100.
我可是專業的
I'm what you call a professional.
實力可是要花錢的
Quality always costs.
可以嗎
So are we on?
她兩點要去看牙醫
She has a dental appointment at 2:00.
不要讓我看到她回家
I'd be fine with her never coming home.
好的 你要做的就是
Alright, here's what I want you to do.
回店裏呆著 在一目瞭然的地方
Go back to the bar, and stay there, in plain sight.
笑迎所有人 不要表現得太反常
Smile for everyone, and don't act funny.
完事後我會聯繫你的
I'll contact you when it's done.
等你電話
I'll be expecting your call.
傑克
Oh, Jack?
保持通話流暢
Don't go putting that online, now, will you?
露西
Lucy.
我做不了
I can't go through with it.
為什麼
Can't?
該死
Shit.
盡量讓他滿意
Whatever he wants, get rid of him.
我來解決
I'll handle it.
布魯斯 你好嗎？
G'day, Bruce. How are you going?
我昨晚解決了個大事情 碰見了一個我們都認識的出版商
I was up the big smoke last night. Met a bookmaker we all know.
-誰  -伊凡布萊克
- Who's that? - Evan Black.
-你認識伊凡嗎  -是我一個親戚
- You know Evan? - He's a relative.
是嗎
I had no idea.
你知道
You know how it is around here.
我們總是和一些人有千絲萬縷的聯繫
We're all related one way or another.
是呀 世界真小
Yeah. Small world.
伊凡說你在躲他
Evan says you've been avoiding him.
說你欠他一筆錢
Says you owe him heaps of money,
到現在還沒有還錢的意思
and so far you haven't made good on a single marker.
聽著 我會還錢的
Look, it's okay. I am gonna pay him.
-我承諾過他了  -承諾頂屁用
- I gave him my word. - Fuck your word.
他只想要錢
He wants his money.
我會還錢的 我發誓
And he will get it, on my oath.
你不尊重他
You disrespected him.
他找了一個打手
He arranged for the lads to come see you.
但是我勸住他了
But I talked him out of it.
我先來見你
I said I'd come see you first.
我答應他先拿走你的東西
Promised him I'd collect everything you owe.
這一周內
Within the week.
如果解決不了... 我就殺了你
Failing that... I'd kill you meself.
布魯斯 我們有錢
Bruce... we're good for the money.
我們快要有錢了
Well, we will be.
你再給我一點時間
I just need a little bit more time.
多久
How much time?
兩個月
Couple of months.
-你在跟我開玩笑麼  -不
- You're taking the piss. - No.
短短幾個月怎麼拿到那麼多錢
Where's this money coming from in a few months?
我不能說 但是我發誓
I can't tell you, but it is real, okay? I promise.
別他媽跟我廢話
Don't come the raw fuckin' prawn.
你只有一個星期時間
You've got one week.
這可是25萬啊
We're talking about near 250 grand.
那是以前
That was before.
-什麼以前  -在我之前
- Before what? - Me.
現在是多少
How much now?
現在?
Now?
利滾利之後大概30萬 可以這麼說
Now we're talking about a figure so close to $300,000 we may as well call it that.
我沒說算利息啊 你瘋了嗎
No, we never agreed to that. Are you insane?
-沒有商量的餘地 -你別跟我開玩笑了
- Non-negotiable. - You can't be serious.
我可是很嚴肅的 過來
Let me show you how serious I am. Come here.
不 不用了
Nah, it's alright.
-布魯斯 別這樣  -別讓我說兩次
- Bruce, please. - Don't have me ask twice.
布魯斯 布魯斯
Bruce! Bruce!
你只有一個星期
You've got one week.
回答我
Now, say it.
布魯斯 住手
Bruce, stop.
你覺得他聽懂了嗎
You think he got the message?
-嗯  -聽懂了
- Well? - Yes.
布魯斯 我知道了 給我一個星期的時間
Bruce, we get it, okay? We've got a week.
不然呢
Or else?
我在問你
I'm asking you.
不然…
Or...
你會殺了我們
You'll kill us.
一個星期之內準備好錢
Have the money in a week.
露西 對不起
Lucy, I'm sorry.
別碰我
Don't touch me!
你只是站在那
You just stood there.
我不知道事情會變成這樣
I didn't mean for any of this to happen.
繼續說說這件事
We go ahead with it.
我們需要那筆保險金
We need that insurance money more than ever now.
好
Okay.
你去哪了 我要遲到了
Where have you been? I'm late.
兜了個風
Went for a drive.
我車鑰匙呢
My car keys?
再見 愛麗絲
Goodbye, Alice.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God!
媽的 不
Shit! No!
你覺得他們的房子怎麼樣
How do you like their house?
你確定他們在國外嗎
Are you certain they're overseas?
要待六個月
For the next six months.
你知道密碼嗎
You do know the code, don't you?
馬克斯告訴我一個簡單好記的方法
Max told me there was an easy way to remember it.
是嗎
Obviously.
貝多芬
Beethoven.
-什麼  -密碼
- What? - The code.
1812 1812序曲
It's 1812, after the overture.
那可是柴可夫斯基寫的 傻逼
That's Tchaikovsky, you idiot.
該死
Shit.
露西 你有誰的聯繫方式嗎
Lucy, have you got any of my contacts here?
有
Yeah.
在我化妝包裏 找到了
In my toiletry bag. I'll get it.
那是什麼
What's that?
我打算告訴你的
I was gonna tell you about it.
剛才等你的時候在她車上找到的
I found it in her car when I was waiting for you earlier.
之前的事情搞得我忘了
It just slipped my mind with all that was going on.
有多少錢
How much?
大概25萬
About...$250,000.
一百萬的四分之一
Quarter of a million dollars.
你把這錢忘記了
And you just forgot about it?
我們沒必要殺了她
We didn't have to kill her, did we?
你在說什麼
What are you talking about?!
我們可以用這些錢還布魯斯
We could have used that money to pay Bruce.
在我找到之前 我們還欠了一大筆債
By the time I found it, we were already committed.
真容易
Very convenient.
沒什麼是很容易
Believe me, there is nothing convenient
我們要收拾的是你的爛攤子
about this mess that you got us into!
嘿
Hey.
我受不了只有這麼點錢
I'm sick and tired of having barely enough.
我想要更多
I want more.
你也是
So should you.
我要走了
I'm off.
為什麼要走
Why? Why do you have to leave?
有機會我會回來的
I'll come back when I get a chance.
好吧
Okay.
你拿著包幹嘛
Why are you taking that?
把他放在安全的地方
I'll keep it safe.
你好傑克
Hello, Jack.
-是你   -是我
- You. - Me.
幹完了?
Is it done?
沒幹完我不會回來的
I wouldn't be here if it weren't.
她死了嗎
She's dead?
-你怎麼辦的 -很簡單
- How'd you do it? - Oh, easy there, Jack.
你最好別知道了
The less you know, the better.
在種種問題前面你沒辦法說謊
That way, if people start asking questions, you don't have to lie.
-她…  -死了
- She's... - Gone.
永遠的消失了
Forever.
你打算醉生夢死嗎
You planning on drinking yourself to death, Jack?
也許吧
Maybe.
那是你的事情
Your business is your own.
我們把賬算一算
As long as we're square.
有什麼證據證明她死了
You got some proof for me?
不然我怎麼相信你
Or am I supposed to just take your word?
什麼 你不相信我
What, you don't trust me anymore?
我以為她死了你會很高興
I'd have thought you'd be glad to be rid of her.
解決了你所有難題
Answer to all your problems.
不管你怎麼想
Despite what you think,
我很愛我的妻子
I love my wife very much.
非常愛
Too much.
非常棒 你的示愛方式真瘋狂
Well, you've got a crazy way of showing it.
因為她出軌了
Nobody makes a fool out of me.
錢沒了
It's gone.
我可不喜歡聽到這個
I don't like the sound of that.
愛麗絲
Alice.
別玩我 傑克
You wouldn't be playing games with me, would you, Jack?
什麼
What?
別擔心 我還有很多
No, don't worry. I have more.
在哪
Where?
在銀行最安全的箱子裏
At the safety deposit box at the bank.
嚇了我一跳
Had me worried for a moment.
明天我什麼時候來拿
What time shall I come back tomorrow?
三點之後
Give me till 3:00.
兩點吧
Let's make it 2:00.
傑克 說了這麼多 我都渴了
Jack, all this talk of booze has got me quite thirsty.
你知道在這附近有什麼酒吧嗎
You wouldn't know of any good bars in the area, would you?
媽的
Shit.
嘿 布魯斯
Hi, Bruce.
露西去哪了
Where's Lucy?
他還沒來上班
Oh, she hasn't showed up for work yet.
你知道我來這的目的嗎
You know why I'm here?
知道
Yeah.
我有一個星期的時間
You said I had a week, so that gives me at least...
別逗我
Don't play games.
我來執行公務
I'm here on police business.
發生了一場車禍你知道嗎
You know anything about a crash?
魔鬼巖那條路上
Up on Devil's Rocks Road?
我不知道啊
No. Should I?
我不覺得你有這個膽子
I didn't think you had the balls, mate.
我聽不懂你在說什麼
What are you talking about?
我找到了露西的車子 或者說是殘骸
I found Lucy's car, or what's left of it.
這些事情都在保險範圍之內
This thing has insurance job written all over it.
別想騙我
Don't bullshit me.
你保險單上有你妻子的名字嗎
You got a policy in your wife's name?
有
Yes.
我聽說
Well, one word from me in the wrong man's ear
殺人可不能賠償
and that claim won't clear for a bloody long time.
但是在我的立場上 這件事
But I'm also in a position to make this thing
顯而易見
go your way without a hitch, open and shut case.
但在這件事上 我需要得到一些補償
But for these services, I need to be compensated.
你說
I'm listening.
-我要一半   -一半？
- I want half. - Half?
你還清債務之後剩下的錢裏 我要一半
Half of what's left after you settle your debts.
不可能
No way!
考慮到你的處境 南森
Consider your options, Nathan.
我已經很慷慨了 別逼我
Okay? I'm being very generous. Don't insult me.
你有你妻子的牙科病歷嗎
You got a copy of your wife's dental records?
拿來給我複印一份
Hey? Save me a trip back here after I ring this in.
好吧
Yes.
給你
Here.
我真是小看你了
I underestimated you, mate.
這可是你老婆
Your own wife.
你可真狠心
You're a heartless fucker.
露西
Luce.
Lucy!
露西
出了點問題
Bit of a problem.
看看這個
Read this.
你什麼時候收到的
When did you get this?
挺早的時候
Earlier.
知道誰發送的嗎？
Do you have any idea who sent it?
不知道
No.
你知道嗎
Do you?
啥 都說了不知道了
What? Of course not.
25萬美元
Two hundred and fifty thousand dollars.
不覺得像是巧合嗎
Bit of a coincidence, don't you think?
郵件說他在看著我們
The email says he's watching us.
看誰
He?
你覺得是個女的嗎
Oh, you think it's a she?
也許吧
Maybe.
-你可真搞笑  -我搞笑嗎
- You're being ridiculous. - Am I?
不管是男是女 這裏提到了25萬美金
Well, he or she, all they mention here is 250 grand.
所以呢
So?
很明顯他們不知道保險的事
So obviously they don't know about the insurance policy
不然不要更多
or they'd be after a lot more.
你覺得我們要給嗎
You think we should pay?
媽的
Fuck.
我們可以先解決這個金額較少的
I think we have a chance to end this cheap.
少麼
Cheap?
比較來說
In comparison.
不然我們沒有別的選擇
Besides, I don't see too many options.
也許吧
Maybe.
你還有錢吧
You still have the money, don't you?
在車上
In the car.
怎麼了
Why?
擔心你會揮霍一空
Thought maybe you'd gambled it away already.
又開始了
Don't start.
-你要去嗎  -去哪
- You coming? - Where?
你說去哪
Where do you think?
我已經死了 記得?
I'm dead, remember?
她在哪
Where is she?
過來
Come here.
你特麼以為自己是誰
Who the fuck do you think you are
居然敢跑來責問我
coming in here accusing me of what, exactly?
我要讓你知道你幹了什麼
I want to know what you did.
那你又幹了什麼
What about what you did?
我還有剩下的
I had you followed.
-我想要回我的錢  -什麼錢
- I want my money back. - What money?
我知道她拿走了我的錢 給了你
I know she took it, I know she gave it to you,
我想要回來
and I want it back.
我沒拿你的錢
I haven't got your money.
是嗎
Is that right?
你在找這個嗎
You looking for this?
她在哪
Where is she?
你要打死我嗎
You gonna shoot me?
告訴我她在哪
Just tell me where she is.
操你媽
Fuck you.
啊
Argh!
啊 臥槽
Argh! Fuck!
你還真開槍 疼死爹了
You fucking shot me! You fucking prick!
她在哪
Where is she?!
我不知道
I don't know!
他沒告訴我
He wouldn't tell me.
哪個他?
Who?
我雇了一個傢伙 他拍了視頻
The guy I hired. The one who shot the video!
-他特麼叫什麼名字  -沃爾夫 查理沃爾夫
- What's his fucking name? - Wolfe! Charlie Wolfe!
去哪能找到他
Where can I find him?
就在這裏 過一會
Here, a little later.
為什麼
Why?
他要來拿酬勞
He still has to get paid.
什麼酬勞
Paid for what?
讓她消失的酬勞
Making her disappear.
他長什麼樣
How will I recognize him?
他開一輛托羅納多
He drives a Toronado.
-那個遊客麼  -他不是遊客
- The tourist. - Yeah, he's no tourist.
我要怎麼做？
So, how are we gonna do this?
很容易
Well, that's the easy part.
你只要把錢放在地上
You just put the money on the ground
進你的車子然後特麼的滾蛋
and then get in your car and fuck off.
這可不行
Not a chance.
我親手來拿
We do this face-to-face or not at all.
事情可沒那麼簡單
You don't get to call the shots.
這是首付
You consider this a down payment.
我先保存著儲存卡
I'll keep the memory card
直到你的保險金拿到手
until the insurance policy's cleared.
除非我死
Over my dead body.
你妻子不是死了嗎
Isn't that over your wife's dead body?
去死吧你
You go to hell!
你可真不禮貌
You've got a bad attitude.
瞧 這是給你的錢
Look, your money is here,
我在這裏等你過來拿
and so am I until you come and collect it.
或者我直接開槍
Or I could just shoot you where you stand,
然後去拿錢
come and take the money.
怎麼了 你要殺掉唯一一個能拿到保險金的人嗎
What, and kill the only person that can claim the insurance policy?
我可不這麼想
I don't think so.
-很好  -媽的
- Yes! - Fuck!
臥槽
Fuck!
我不是很想殺了你的
You know, I'd prefer not to kill you.
但是我還是會
But I will.
我們倆清了
Just so we're clear.
-放過我  -不管你說什麼
- This ends today. - Whatever you say.
上帝啊
God!
媽的
Fuck!
你覺得很有趣嗎
Do you find something funny?!
你可真是個瘋子 你知道嗎
You're a fucking lunatic! You know that?
-看看包裏  -什麼
- Look in the bag. - Why?
我想看看你的表情
'Cause I want to see your face.
你妻子那
That wife of yours.
有點什麼 對吧
She's something, right?
別碰她
Leave her alone.
告訴我錢在哪 不然我就讓她挨槍子
Tell me where the fucking money is or she eats this gun.
我告訴你的話...
If I tell you...
我就不會殺她
Then I won't kill her.
-你保證  -我發誓
- Give me your word. - I promise.
在後備箱
It's in the boot.
鑰匙在我口袋裏
The keys are... in my pocket.
-現在…  -什麼
- Now... - Yeah?
我會告訴你妻子
...I will be sure to tell your wife
你努力為她做的一切
what you tried to do for her.
你發過誓的
You promised me.
你發誓...
You promised...
不
No.
No!
傑克
Jack?
我要渴死了
I could murder a drink.
不管這看起來怎樣 我跟這可沒關系
Despite how this looks, I had nothing to do with it.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey! Hey!
迪倫
Dylan!
崩
Boo!
媽的
Fuck!
你在這特麼的做啥
What the fuck are you doing here?
該死的
Dammit!
發生了什麼事
What happened?
他刺傷我了
He fucking stabbed me.
什麼 南森
What, Nathan?
是啊 完全就是個瘋子
Yeah. What a complete psycho.
-你拿到錢了嗎  -對 我拿到了
- But you got the money? - Oh, I got it.
南森去哪了
Where's Nathan now?
我就想說這個
Yeah, about that.
-什麼   -呃...
- What about it? - Um...
你搞砸了嗎
Did you fuck this up?
親愛的 我今天過得很糟糕
Honey, I'm having a bad day here.
你把他殺了
You killed him?
他弄傷了我的手
He forced my hand.
你知道你在幹什麼嗎
Do you realize what you've done?
這不怪我啊 對不起
It was him or me, okay? Sorry.
混蛋 查理
Dammit, Charlie!
你想他死啊
You wanted him dead.
-是啊 在拿到保險及以後 -我能怎麼辦 那傢伙瘋了
- Yeah, after the insurance settlement. - What can I say? The guy flipped.
真特麼難以置信 你的工作這麼容易你還搞砸了
Un-fucking-believable. You had a simple job and you fucked it up.
別怪我 是你等不及了
Don't try to blame this on me. You're the one who couldn't wait.
你想要25萬 然後我解決了
You wanted the 250 now, so I sorted it.
解決了？
Sorted it?
不是讓你殺了他 你這傻逼
You weren't meant to kill him, you idiot!
好好說話
Watch your mouth.
沒有南森我們怎麼才能拿到保險金
How the fuck do we get the insurance money without Nathan?
托你的福我們的計劃全亂了
Thanks to your incompetence, our plan's utterly ruined.
這下真好 查理
That's just great, Charlie.
你丈夫可以忍受你我可不能
Your husband might have put up with your shit.
別把我跟他扯一塊去
Don't mistake me for him.
這是我榮幸
Well, I'd like to say it's been a pleasure.
你什麼意思
What do you mean?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
好 我跟你一起走
Yeah, I'm coming with you.
-這輩子都不行  -你不能就這麼走了
- Not in this life. - You can't just leave.
不然你想怎樣
What were you expecting?
-但是...  -但是我們上過床了?
- But... - What, because we fucked?
當做是我給你的額外福利好了
Consider it a fringe benefit.
先分錢
We split the money first.
別這麼貪財
No need to be greedy.
你會繼承酒店的
You're about to inherit the hotel.
你說什麼
What are you talking about?
你會知道的
You'll see.
知道什麼？
I'll see what?
再見 親愛的
So long, honey.
-把儲存卡給我    -什麼
- Give me the card! - What?
儲存卡 給我相機儲存卡
The card! The memory card from the camera.
給我
Give it to me!
你是我見過的最聰明或者最瘋狂的女人
You are either the craziest or the cleverest bitch I have ever met.
我不能決定是哪個
I can't decide.
搞什麼
What the fuck?!
迪倫 你在這幹嘛
Dylan, what are you doing here?
我也要問你
I could ask you the same thing.
天啊 這地方就是個露天瘋人院
God, this place is like a fucking open-air insane asylum!
-這就算你拿到的酬勞嗎  -什麼酬勞
- Is this what you did it for? - Did what?
別裝傻 傑克都告訴我了
Don't play dumb. Jack filled me in on your deal.
不 你誤會了
No, look, you've got it all wrong.
-少他媽說謊  -我沒碰她一根汗毛
- Don't fucking lie. - I didn't touch her.
他騙人 是他幹的 是他殺了愛麗絲
He's lying. He did it. He killed Alice.
你這個婊子
You fucking snake!
他還殺了南森
And he killed Nathan.
對 是她殺了愛麗絲 她殺的
Look, if you want to know who killed Alice, she did.
迪倫 我發誓…
Dylan, I swear to God...
我能證明
Look, I can prove it.
-他在說謊  -閉嘴
- He's lying! - Shut the fuck up!
我知道是你殺了她
I know you killed her.
她死了 你也得死
She's dead, and so are you.
射的好
Nice shot!
我...
I...
射偏了
Fuck's sake.
是時候送你遠離痛苦了
Time we put you out of your misery.
不 不 不 不
No, no! No! No!
是我拿的錢
I took the money.
我知道
I know.
怎麼了
What?
喂?
Yeah?
我一個小時後到
I'll be there in an hour.
不如兩個小時吧
Better make that two.
臥槽
Fuck's sake.